Don Wright Papers
Don Wright Papers
- Cartoons
  - Undated
    - C (oversize mounted) (Oversize 5)
      [Capsules Returned Safely]: space exploration
    - D (Oversize 3)
      D—Don't Let Them Take Me Again!: Republican Party, right wing politics, George. W. Romney
      [Dade Seaport]
      [Dade Voter]: elections
      Dear Ho Chi Minh: Mao Zedong
      [Demo Platform]: Barry Goldwater
      [Death Toll]: traffic fatalities
      Dick Nixon Gave Me This, Right, Dick? Dick! Hey Dick!: Barry Goldwater
      [Diem]: Buddhism
      Discordant Notes: Barry Goldwater
      Don't Forget Who's In Charge Here: Sukarno
      Don't Misunderstand Me, I Have Nothing Against Lady Bird's Beautification Program—: Air Force 1
    - E (Oversize 3)
      Eeeeeeeeeeeeeya! Let's Go Get 'Em, Men!: Cuba, Barry Goldwater
      Ejection Seat: Lyndon B. Johnson, Bobby Baker
      End Of The Trail: Congress
      —Er, Any Old Business?: bribery, metro commission, Miami
      —Er, No! The Name Of The Show Isn't 'Beat The Press!’: Ngo Dinh Nhu
      Exodus: Lyndon B. Johnson, Ted Sorensen, Arthur M. Schlesinger, Jr., Pierre Salinger, Richard Hatcher
      [Extreme Right]: Minutemen
    - F (Oversize 3)
      Fallout: China, nuclear weapons
      Farris Bryant, Do You Solemnly Sweah—: George Wallace, Orval Faubus, Ross Barnett
      Fastest President In The West
      For All The Critics: Robert McNamara
      Fortress, Latin America: Venezuela
      Frankly, I'm Worried, He's Healthy As A Horse: economy
    - F (oversize mounted) (Oversize 5)
      [Flu Bug]
    - G (Oversize 3)
      [Gandhi's peace try, Wilson's peace try]: Soviet Union, Harold Wilson, Indira Gandhi
      Gee I Used To Go There and Sit!: Miami railroad depot
      Gee! What Could Poor Little Old Me Do?: refugees, kidnaping
      Georgia Peaches: Lester Maddox
      Go Right Ahead. I Won't Interfere: Dwight D. Eisenhower, Barry Goldwater
      [Goldwater Dike]: Barry Goldwater
      [Goldwater statements]: Barry Goldwater, press
      [Gov't. Report on Smoking]
      Ground To Air Missiles: Fidel Castro, armed forces
    - G (oversize mounted) (Oversize 5)
      Gimme One Good Objection To Compulsory Unionism: New York City, transit strike, right to work law
      Go In Peace—Every Chance You Get: New Year's 1966
      [The Great Debate]: Vietnam War
      [The Great Leap Forward]: nuclear weapons, China
    - H (Oversize 3)
      He Said Merry Christmas And Happy New Year—Or Else: Fidel Castro
      Heap of Reading: John Birch Society
      Heat Wave: race riots
      Heeeeeyaaaaaa! Geeeeeyap! Hoooooyahhh!: racism, Haydon Burns
      Hello In There—Remember Me?: Vietnam War, United Nations
      [Herbert Hoover (1874- 1964)]
      He's Gone Rational On Us: Barry Goldwater, Ku Klux Klan
      He's Still A Little Reluctant: California, Barry Goldwater
      Hey! You Guys Ain't My Tailors Yet!: Jimmy Hoffa
      Hi, Y'all!: Nelson Rockefeller, Barry Goldwater
      High Pockets: Charles De Gaulle, gold
      [Holiday Traffic Toll]: traffic fatalities
      Hmmmm?: Brake
      How Do I Tell Him He Can't Keep It?: Republican Party
      [Hubert Humphrey Best Supporting Role]
      Humor Him. It Might Be His Last Convention: American South
      Hurricane Watch: weather
    - H (oversize mounted) (Oversize 5)
      [House Un-American Activities Committee and Federal Grand Jury Tackling A Ku Klux Klan Sheet ]
      Household Item: Vietnam War
    - I - J (Oversize 3)
      I Bet You Thought I'd Never Get Here: inflation, taxes
      I Can Fly! I Can Fly! I Can—: France, NATO
      I Could Just Love Him To Death!: Barry Goldwater
      I Do Not Imbibe: George W. Romney, Barry Goldwater
      I Only Wear It On Certain Occasions: democracy, Latin America
      I Remember It Was 1966 And Somebody Said 'No Sanctuary.' Then Everything Went Blank.:
      I Said, Support! Support! S-U-P-P-O-R-T! Like In George Hamilton's Mother—: Vietnam War
      I thought you'd never find me!: Supreme Court, urban voters
      I Wonder What Makes It So Controversial: Bible, schools
      I'll Just Shake Him A Little: Perez Jimenez, Venezuela
      I'll Meet You Half Way: Fidel Castro
      In Pro Football, Rookies, We Have One Basic Play: draft, armed forces
      [Integration Drive]
      Internal Disorder: China
      It Burns A Little!: Doyle Carlton
      It Used To Be So Cuddly: Indonesia, China
      It's From George Wallace, Gang! We're Gonna Start A Third Party
      It's Gone Berserk!: Congress, Lyndon B. Johnson
      It's Great For Sticking People, Too: John Birch Society
      Just When It Was Getting Brighter: Vietnam War, Lyndon B. Johnson
      [Justice Douglas weds 23 year old, Sinatra weds 21 year old]
    - I (oversize mounted) (Oversize 5)
      I'm Ronald Reagan—Welcome To 'Death Valley Days: Barry Goldwater, California, Republican Party
      I'm The Favorite Tonight: University of Miami, football
      [India's Food Supply]: Indira Gandhi
      The Iron Curtain: Berlin Wall
    - K (Oversize 3)
      Kelly In A Gun—Duel With Me Nayr
    - K (oversize mounted) (Oversize 5)
      Knock Off That 'Holy Spendthrift Stuff!
    - L (Oversize 3)
      Let Us Begin Again: U. Thant, United Nations, Vietnam War
      Let's Hop In Your Car And Speed Over To My Place: traffic fatalities
      Let's Stop It Before He Kills Himself: boxing
      Light In The Jungle: Vietnam War, elections
      The Light Is Out: India, Jawaharlal Nehru
      Limousine: Miami mayor
      A Little Coaxing, and I might squeeze into those: George Wallace (1965)
      Little Does He Know He'll Soon Be Extinct!: Barry Goldwater
      Lobbyist: Congress, civil rights
      [Longshoreman's Union—Miami Local]
      [Look!! The Great Missile—Bomber Gap!!]: Barry Goldwater
      Lord Whom?: Rab Butler, Reginald Maudling, Lord Hailsham
    - M (Oversize 3)
      [Mac Arthur]: Douglas MacArthur
      [Machinists strike]: economy
      March On, Brother, It's A Free Road: civil rights
      —Maybe Even Deeper: Martin Luther King Jr., bigotry, North, South
      Maybe We Can Back It Through Congress!: civil rights, Robert F. Kennedy, John F. Kennedy
      [McNamara and TFX]: Robert McNamara
      McNamara Stepped On The Other One: Barry Goldwater
      [Mexico]: Lyndon B. Johnson
      [Miami Weather Bureau ]
      Moooooooo—o—o—oney!
      Moonlighters: University of Miami, government
      Motherhood: nuclear weapons, China
      Move Over, Buster: space exploration
      Must Be One Of Us—You're White: George Wallace
    - N (Oversize 3)
      [ Negotiate]: Ho Chi Minh
      Never Saw That Mountain: Nguyen Cao Ky
      Never Touched Me: Adam Clayton Powell
      [New Metro Commission]: cities, Florida
      Next, We'll Get Rid Of That Thing!: Brake, voting
      [90th Congress and Great Society]
      1968? Whatever Gave You That Idea?: Richard Nixon
      No Lyndon, I Will NOT Skip Bobby Kennedy's House!: Robert F. Kennedy, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Nonsense, Hubert. I Wouldn't Trade You For Anybody: Hubert Humphrey, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Nothing Personal, Podnuhs: Dade county, T.A. Buchannan, Charles Zmuda, George Leppig
      Notice The Difference When We Throw Our Weight Around?: civil rights
      Now Who Do We Pick On? :Barry Goldwater, cartoonists
      Nuclear Disaster: nuclear weapons, United Nations
    - N (oversize mounted) (Oversize 5)
      The 1965 Voting Rights Act Has Been Upheld To Insure EQUALITY
    - O (Oversize 3)
      [OAS Sanctions]: Organization of American States
      O'boy! A White Christmas!: Miami, retail sales
      [Office Of County Mgr[.: Dade County, Florida
      Oh, Excuse Me! You Say You're Buddhist Anti-American, Not Viet Cong Anti-American: Vietnam War
      Oh, No! You Get Together With Me!: Florida, cities
      [Oil Globs]
      —One Of Those Wild-Eyed Harvard Boys!
      Oops! Right Downtown: bombs
      Out! Or We'll Ram You And Hurt Ourselves!: Panama Canal, Lyndon B. Johnson
    - P-Q (Oversize 3)
      Pall Taxed
      The Peasantry-Riding MY Trains!: Ed Ball
      Peddler: guns
      Pipsqueak!: nature nuclear weapons, Alaska
      Poll Taxed: elections
      [Poor or uneducated youths, smart college students]: Lewis Blaine Hershey
      Popularity Ratings: Robert F. Kennedy, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Power Struggle? Heck, No Whoops! This Thing Keeps Falling Off: Mao Zedong
      [The Press]: Lyndon B. Johnson
      Pressure Gauge: Barry Goldwater
      Pull Down To Ignite: Lyndon B. Johnson, Barry Goldwater
      [Pure White Dairy]
      Quickie Reassessment: Dade county, housing
    - P (oversize mounted) (Oversize 6)
      [Peace by Shastri]: Lal Bahadur Shastri
      Peace Feelers: Vietnam War
      [Peking Trade Pact]: China, Fidel Castro
      Plastic Planes? Plastic Tanks? Aw, Come On, Lyndon!: steel industry
    - R (Oversize 4)
      Rabid Fire: Lyndon B. Johnson
      [Racial Chaos]: George Wallace, civil rights
      [Racial Dispute]: George Wallace
      Racial Intolerance
      [Reassessment Windfall]: schools, Florida
      [Red China]
      Rembrandt: state universities, communism
      Remember That Yankee Joke About Carrying Big Stick?: Mao Zedong, Vietnam War
      Reopened For Approval: Florida legislature
      [Report Of The Warren Commission On The Assassination of President Kennedy]
      [Republican National Convention—1964]: Barry Goldwater, John Birch Society
      Retirement Looks Good On You Comrade: Nikita Khrushchev
      [Rigged Ballot]: amendments
      ROAR!(possibly Castro's head on a mouse's body)
      Ronald!: Ronald Reagan, California, Republican Party, Richard Nixon
      [Ruby]
      Runt!: space exploration, Sputnik
    - R (oversize mounted) (Oversize 6)
      Remember, Lurleen, There Are Four Basic Positions For Blocking A University Doorway: George Wallace
    - S (Oversize 4)
      Say, Who's Your Tailor?: Central Intelligence Agency, state department
      [School Desegregation]: George Wallace, Alabama Legislature
      [Scott Kelly]: Miami
      The Second Exit: civil rights
      See How Many Are Staying On Our Side?: Berlin Wall, Nikita Khrushchev
      Sell TVA: Barry Goldwater, Tennessee Valley Authority
      [Senators Investigating Senators]: Congress
      Sidewalks of New York: crime
      [Slag Steel Company]: steel industry, money
      —Sleepy, You Are Getting Sleepy—You Saw Nothing In The Skies—: UFOs
      Smile Rover, Show 'Em You Ain't Dead: industry, Dade county
      [Smile!—You're on Candid Camera]: space exploration, aliens
      Snip Judgment: Perez Jimenez
      So Help Me, I Never Took My Eyes Off Him!: Barry Goldwater
      So Mild, So Refreshing, Stupid!: smoking
      Somehow, People Didn't Get The Message: hate
      Something's Rotten In Miami: Haydon Burns
      South Dade...458 Magnum... Hundred Yards: hunting
      Sovereignty: civil rights, Mississippi
      S-S-S- Somebody C-Call A Doctor: Medicare, Republican Party
      St. Patrick's Day: world affairs
      [Stock market and news]
      [STOP! Go Back to January 23 ...U.S. Gov't. ]: railroad industry
      [Stop, Sober?, Go ]: drunk driving
      Stray :Congress
      [Strikebound airlines]: airline industry, Congress
      Succession: John McCormack
      Suicide: smoking
      Suicide Gap: baseball
      A Supermarket Boycott Might YOUR Inflation
      Survivor: Barry Goldwater, Ronald Reagan
    - S (oversize mounted) (Oversize 6)
      Steady, Down There: taxes, Vietnam War, Great Society, Lyndon B. Johnson
    - T (Oversize 4)
      Tal, We're In This Thing Together: Haydon Burns, Miami
      Taps Off Diplomacy: Fidel Castro, Lyndon B. Johnson
      [Tax Assessor]: taxes
      Temperature Change: Barry Goldwater, South
      [Test Ban]: nuclear weapons
      Thank Heaven! You're Still Looking Up!: Robert McNamara, Vietnam War
      [That Rascal Castro Exports Revolution!]: Fidel Castro, Organization of American States
      They Serve The Cutest Desserts At These Things: Claude Clutch
      They Smell Like Mine!: Bobby Baker, Congress
      Things Could Be Worse! We Could Be Living In Philadelphia Mississippi!: Africa
      This Has All The Earmarks Of A Communist Conspiracy: Nikita Khrushchev, John Birch Society
      This One Never Fails To Launch: national debt
      Thrown Any Good Coups Lately?
      Tiger In Your Tank: United Auto Workers (1965)
      [To Lyndon From All Your Buddies in the House]: foreign aid
      Tourist Attraction: St. Augustine, Florida, racism
      Tsk, Tsk! I Wonder How It Happened: New York Herald Tribune, unions
    - T (oversize mounted) (Oversize 6)
      Take Me To Your Leader: Lyndon B. Johnson, farming
      Those Dirty Commies! And Her With Two Busted Arms!: Soviet Union, space exploration, Venus de Milo
      Truce: Vietnam War
    - U-V (Oversize 4)
      [U.S. Space Records]: space exploration, Soviet Union
      Under The Anesthesia, He Dreamt He Was Run Over By A Herd Of Elephants: Lyndon B. Johnson
      Unity: Barry Goldwater
      [Unpledged GOP Delegates]: Barry Goldwater, Republican Party, Florida
      Upper Hand: Nguyen Cao Ky
      [Viet Crisis—Cyprus Crisis Ping Pong]: Cyprus, Vietnam War
      [Viet Nam]: Lyndon B. Johnson
      Viet Nam and Cyprus Lighting Bolts: Cyprus, Vietnam War
      [Viet Nam Policy]: Vietnam War, Barry Goldwater, William Scranton
      Vive La France: Charles De Gaulle, Vietnam War
      Volcano: Harlem
    - U (oversize mounted) (Oversize 6)
      [U.S. Peace Offensive]
      Uneasy Street: Wall Street
    - W (Oversize 4)
      Wanted by FBI: Robert F. Kennedy
      [Warren Commission Report ]
      We're Gaining In The War—There's Just One Gap We Haven't Been Able To Close: Nguyen Cao Ky
      We're Not Allowed To Get Involved In The Internal Affairs Of A Foreign Country: Vietnam War
      We Must Be Selective About Those Who Elect Us: voting
      —Weaving In And Out, Following Another Vehicle Too Closely etc.: space exploration
      Weeping Dove: John F. Kennedy assassination
      Well, Back To The Old Grind: left wing politics, right wing politics
      [West German Bundestag]: Nazism
      What Are They Trying To Do, Over—Live?: nuclear weapons, Nikita Khrushchev, Lyndon B. Johnson
      What Do You Suppose Is Causing All These Accidents?: traffic engineers
      What My Party Needs Is A New Face: Richard Nixon, Barry Goldwater
      What Noise?: railroad industry, Farris Bryant
      Wheeeeeeeeeeee! :machinists union, economy
      Wheeeeee! Look at Them Ants Run For Cover: Mendel Rivers, Richard Russell
      Where Do We Surrender?: poverty
      —With Lots OF New, Grander-Than-Ever Gadjets: automobile industry
      [Worthington Case ]
      Wretched Little Devil Knows I Have A Heart Of Gold: Fidel Castro
    - Y-Z (Oversize 4)
      —Yeah, He's Giving Me A Headache, Too: Stokely Carmichael, civil rights (1966)
      The Year Of The Plague: hurricanes (1964)
      Yes, Sir, This Is Where You Change Your Party Affiliation: Abraham Lincoln, voting
      Yes, Sonny, That's Where Congress Sits...And Sits, And Sits!: Congress
      You Are Much Too Fat: Great Society
      You Believe In Omens?
      You Heard Me, George. Go Home And Start Supper: Lurleen Wallace, George Wallace
      You're Un-American!: Vietnam War, protestors, HUAAC
      You're In No Condition To Take Over: elections, Nguyen Cao Ky
      You're On Your Own!: Charles De Gaulle, France, NATO
      Zoooooooooom!: Dade county, highway construction, Florida
    - Y (oversize mounted) (Oversize 6)
      Yeah—Things Are Really Looking Up: economy, food prices
      You Haven't Seen It Have You—A Little Round Nuclear Thingamajig?: Spain
      You Think Being A Cosmonaut Is Dangerous—His Old Man Writes Books!: Soviet Union
      Your Skates Or Your Life (New York Transit Strike)
    - Untitled cartoons (Oversize 4)
      [Bear with picks teeth and clutches stomach while "stock market" briefcase sits at his feet]
      [A small Haydon Burns sits on the back of a donkey]
      [Lyndon Johnson pulls a rabbit labeled Manila out of a hat]
      [Harold Wilson pulling belt on oversized pants]
      [Clayton Powell looks at self as light and shadow make his clothes look striped]
      [Mao Zedong swims with casts "Indonesia" and "North Korea" on his feet]
      [Lyndon Johnson dips toe into water labeled "1968"]
      [Lightning strikes over the Beatles]
      [Charles De Gaulle as a peace dove]
      [Earth reaches out with a ladder to the moon]
      [McNayr vs. Kelly in a gun fight]
      [Lyndon Johnson bounces off a donkey's back]
      [Lyndon Johnson stretches the U.S. dollar]
      [Elephant falls through a platform labeled "civil rights"]
      [Elephant in water labeled "Goldwater" looks at a "Nixon" life preserver]
      [Cobwebs cover a Hanoi and U.S. peace talk table]
      [Chart of high food prices and housewives boycott]
      [World rests on United Nations which rests on U.S. dollar]
      [Bobby Baker as a bee not caught by the Senate]
      [Desert of "politics"s and a Dade County sherif's badge]
      [Jacksonville and Duval County School system]
      [Voter on pedestal over a crowd of candidates]
      [Bryant sticks fingers in ears amidst crime in Jacksonville]
      [Lyndon Johnson in Latin America outside a window with Charles De Gaulle]
      [Supreme Court hand in between "religion" and "public schools" books]
      [Crashed car inside a bottle]
      [Nelson Rockefeller, Barry Goldwater and Richard Nixon as flowers]
      [Man reaches for a tax cut]
      [George Wallace in a parade with a Confederate flag]
      [Lyndon Johnson in a boxing ring with Nikita Khrushchev and Mao Zedong]
      [Barry Goldwater as a snake charmer]
      [Communist hand reaches for wheat]
      [Mao Zedong blows on Southeast Asia fire while nuclear war looms]
      [Two cars marked "accident rate" and "insurance rate"]
      [Central Intelligence Committee and Fulbright Committee represented as figures in dark trench coats, face masks and hats]
    - Untitled cartoons (oversize mounted) (Oversize 6)
      [Economy looks at inflation in the mirror]
      [Lyndon B. Johnson on the brink]
      [Charles De Gaulle runs over NATO in a tank]
      [Great Society and Viet War costs weighed on a scale by the U.S. Capitol]
      [Inter-American Peace Force Dominican]: Dominican Republic
- Correspondence
  - 1963-1965 (Box 1)